So now let's actually look at a real example of someone asking for advice about how to get in shape
所以现在让我们看一个真实的例子，有人询问如何塑形的建议
or get fit and how we can actually give advice to that person.
或变得健康，以及我们如何实际向那个人提供建议。
So two friends talking.
于是两个朋友聊了起来。
I'm having a hard time losing weight.
我很难减肥。
Now we know they're trying.
现在我们知道他们正在努力。
I'm having a hard time.
我很难过。
Hard time means it's difficult.
困难时期意味着困难。
It's difficult having a hard time losing weight even though I don't overeat.
即使我不暴饮暴食，减肥也很难。
We use even though to say that something is kind of against something else I feel thirsty even though
我们用即使说某事有点反对其他我感到口渴即使
I just had a glass of water.
我刚喝了一杯水。
OK.
好的。
I feel happy even though today was actually a pretty terrible day.
即使今天实际上是非常糟糕的一天，我仍然感到高兴。
I feel happy even though it was a bad day.
即使是糟糕的一天，我也感到很开心。
OK so I'm having a hard time losing weight even though I don't overeat.
好吧，即使我没有吃得过多，我也很难减肥。
I don't overeat.
我不会暴饮暴食。
That means I think you can guess eat too much.
这意味着我认为你可以猜到吃太多了。
Could you give me some advice.
你能给我一些建议吗？
That's one of the simple ways to get advice.
这是获得建议的简单方法之一。
Very direct way to get advice that we talked about at the very beginning of this lesson.
获得我们在本课开始时谈到的建议的非常直接的方法。
Now we give the answer we give the advice to our friend and pay attention to some of the phrases that
现在我们给出答案我们给我们的朋友建议并注意一些短语
we learned earlier in the class.
我们在课堂上学过。
Have you tried actually counting calories.
您是否尝试过实际计算卡路里。
Calories are things that we have in food things that we eat which give us energy.
卡路里是我们在食物中所含的东西，我们吃的东西能给我们能量。
But also if we eat too many calories can make us make us fat.
但是，如果我们摄入过多的卡路里也会使我们发胖。
OK.
好的。
Have you tried counting calories OK.
你试过计算卡路里吗？
That means you actually pay attention to how many calories you eat.
这意味着你实际上会注意你吃了多少卡路里。
If so that means if the answer is yes.
如果是这样，这意味着如果答案是肯定的。
If so that's a great way to make sure you aren't overdoing it.
如果是这样，这是确保您没有过度使用它的好方法。
So to overdo something means to do too much of that thing.
因此，过度做某事意味着做太多的事情。
What is overdoing it here overdoing it means eating too much overeating.
什么是过量这里过量它意味着吃太多暴饮暴食。
If you want to know if you're overeating maybe you think you're not overeating maybe you think that
如果你想知道你是否暴饮暴食也许你认为你没有暴饮暴食也许你认为
you don't overeat but maybe really you are maybe you're not eating very often but maybe the foods you're
你没有吃得过饱，但也许你真的是，也许你不经常吃，但也许你吃的食物
eating are very high in calories.
吃的热量非常高。
OK.
好的。
So count calories whenever I need to lose a few pounds.
因此，每当我需要减掉几磅体重时，都要计算卡路里。
So now we use the one that shows that we are sharing our experience and also shows empathy whenever
所以现在我们使用一个表明我们正在分享我们的经验并且在任何时候都表现出同理心的
I need to lose a few pounds.
我需要减掉几磅。
I keep track of all my meals in a diet journal.
我在饮食日记中记录我所有的膳食。
OK.
好的。
So this diet means what we eat is what we eat is our diet our diet is the food that we eat usually.
所以这种饮食意味着我们吃的就是我们吃的就是我们的饮食 我们的饮食就是我们通常吃的食物。
OK keep track of something means you pay attention to it.
好的，跟踪某事意味着您关注它。
You follow it carefully.
你仔细遵循它。
OK.
好的。
Anyway you should definitely try that.
无论如何，您绝对应该尝试一下。
Definitely makes it sound a little stronger.
绝对让它听起来更强大一些。
You should remember.
你应该记住。
You should.
你应该。
Means it's a bit more forceful.
意味着它更强大一些。
You're not saying you could you can you should say a little stronger.
你不是说你能，你应该说强一点。
If that doesn't work you might try fasting.
如果这不起作用，您可以尝试禁食。
This is the same as you could try.
这与您可以尝试的相同。
So you might try you could try is the same.
所以你可以试试你可以试试是一样的。
You might try fasting which I've been reading about lately so fasting means you don't eat for a long
你可以试试我最近读到的禁食，所以禁食意味着你不会吃太久
period of time.
一段的时间。
Someone says I'm fasting.
有人说我在禁食。
That means maybe for this whole day or maybe for a week or whatever they're not eating you don't eat
这意味着可能一整天或一周或任何他们不吃的东西你不吃
for a period of time.
一段时间。
It's called fasting fasting.
这叫做禁食禁食。
People do it for many different reasons.
人们这样做有很多不同的原因。
So let's continue with the advice again.
因此，让我们再次继续建议。
Pay attention to the phrases that we learned earlier in the lesson as far as exercise goes as far as
就练习而言，注意我们在本课前面学到的短语
what does that mean.
这意味着什么。
So sometimes when we want to change the topic and talk about something else we talked about diet.
因此，有时当我们想改变话题并谈论其他事情时，我们会谈论饮食。
Now I want to change and talk about a new thing and we want to say what that new topic is we can use
现在我想改变并谈论一个新事物，我们想说那个新话题是我们可以使用的
as far as or we can also use when it comes to whatever that is when it comes to exercise.
就运动而言，或者我们也可以使用。
As far as exercise goes these are basically the same used to change the topic used to mentioned what
就练习而言，这些基本上是相同的，用于改变用于提到什么的主题
topic we're going to say as far as exercise goes.
就锻炼而言，我们要说的话题。
You should definitely be doing some exercise every day every day.
你绝对应该每天每天都做一些锻炼。
First you can try going for a 30 minute run every morning.
首先，你可以尝试每天早上跑 30 分钟。
And if that doesn't seem to be working after a few weeks we learned if that doesn't work.
如果这在几周后似乎不起作用，我们就会知道这是否不起作用。
But because it's kind of a continuous thing because it's kind of ongoing then we can say if that doesn't
但是因为它是一种持续的事情，因为它是一种持续的事情，所以我们可以说如果那不是
seem to be working OK.
似乎工作正常。
If that doesn't seem to be working after a few weeks go to the gym at least three to four times when
如果几周后这似乎不起作用，那么去健身房至少三到四次
we say when we see this and we read it we say three to four times three to four times a week.
我们说，当我们看到它并阅读它时，我们会说每周三到四次三到四次。
Notice that this doesn't say one week we usually just say a week three to four times a week.
请注意，这并不是说一周，我们通常只说一周三到四次。
And because this is three or four we can actually use or if we want to if it's three to six.
因为这是三到四，我们可以实际使用，或者如果我们想的话，如果它是三到六。
Then we have to say three to six.
然后我们不得不说三到六。
But because these two are side by side we can say three or four five or six six or seven but we can't
但是因为这两个是并排的，所以我们可以说三四五六六七，但我们不能
say three or six because that means you can't go four or five times which is very weird.
说三六次，因为这意味着你不能去四五次，这很奇怪。
OK.
好的。
If that doesn't seem to be working after a few weeks go to the gym at least three to four times a week
如果几周后这似乎不起作用，每周至少去健身房三到四次
and do both cardio and strength training.
并进行有氧运动和力量训练。
Anytime you see the word cardio it's going to be related to your heart or the system in your body where
每当您看到有氧这个词时，它都会与您的心脏或您体内的系统有关
the blood moves pumped by your heart.
血液由你的心脏泵出。
It's usually about heart health.
它通常与心脏健康有关。
So if you run if you jump if you go on a treadmill if you ride a bicycle.
因此，如果您在跑步机上骑自行车，则如果您跳就跑。
This is cardio and strength training is lifting weights lifting weights weight lifting maybe you have
这是有氧运动，力量训练是举重举重举重也许你有
some dumbbells or barbells or whatever you're trying to build muscle build muscle.
一些哑铃或杠铃或任何你想锻炼肌肉的东西。
OK so this is how we can give advice about getting fit getting in shape.
好的，这就是我们如何提供关于健身的建议。
There are many different ways we can do it of course.
当然，我们有很多不同的方法可以做到这一点。
This is just one example but hopefully you have a pretty clear idea for how we can use some of these
这只是一个示例，但希望您对我们如何使用其中一些有一个非常清晰的想法
different phrases to help our friend.
不同的短语来帮助我们的朋友。
So as we usually do when we learn something the best way to make it stick is to actually practice it.
因此，正如我们通常在学习某些东西时所做的那样，让它坚持下去的最好方法就是实际练习它。
If you don't have somebody to practice with.
如果没有人陪练。
I always recommend that you record yourself get your phone out.
我总是建议您录制自己的电话。
Record.
记录。
Record writing is good.
记录写作很好。
OK you can write.
好的，可以写了。
That's fine.
没关系。
But if you write are you really going to be a better English speaker.
但如果你写作，你真的会成为一个更好的英语演讲者吗？
Well they are very different skills.
嗯，他们是非常不同的技能。
You can be a great writer and not a great speaker.
你可以成为一个伟大的作家，而不是一个伟大的演说家。
So I recommend that you get out your phone you turn on the record function and you try to use some of
所以我建议你拿出手机打开录音功能尝试使用一些
the words and phrases that we learned in this lesson for giving advice.
我们在本课中学到的用于提供建议的单词和短语。
The assignment is to imagine that you have a friend who wants to quit smoking.
任务是想象你有一个想戒烟的朋友。
A big problem.
一个大问题。
Addicted to smoking.
沉迷于吸烟。
Your friend is addicted to smoking.
你的朋友对吸烟上瘾。
So he or she has tried many things and everything has been unsuccessful.
所以他或她尝试了很多事情，但一切都没有成功。
Nothing is working.
没有任何工作。
So what advice would you give.
那你会给什么建议。
What advice would you give.
你会给什么建议。
Try to use the words and phrases we learned.
尝试使用我们学到的单词和短语。
Good luck.
祝你好运。